Guide to the Antiquarian bookseller catalog collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Antiquarian bookseller catalog collection.
1747-1993
X346
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1000
(approximately 70,000 volumes)
Antiquarian bookseller catalogs collected by Yale University Library.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transfer from Sterling Memorial Library.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Antiquarian bookseller catalogs collected by Yale University Library.
Arrangement
Arranged by call number.
Antiquarian booksellers -- Catalogs; Auctions catalogs -- 18th century; Auctions catalogs -- 19th century; Auctions catalogs -- 20th Century; Sales catalogs -- 18th century; Sales catalogs -- 19th century; Sales catalogs -- 20th Century
- A
  - X346 A145, 1834; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - T. Albin; Spalding, in Lincolnshire (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - X346 A16, 1931-ca. 1940; nos. 2-82, 61 catalogs
    - Academy Book Shop Inc.; New York City (Box 1, Folder 2-10)
    - Academy Book Shop Inc.; New York City (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
  - X346 A182, undated [early 1930s?]; nos. 2-17, 10 catalogs
    - Ackermann Sauerwein; Frankfurt, München (Box 2, Folder 13-15)
  - X346 A185, 1962-1968; nos. 3-14, 5 catalogs
    - Acme Books; Oakland, California (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - X346 A192, 1964-1969; nos. 1-14, 8 catalogs
    - Ad Orientem; Sussex, England (Box 2, Folder 17-19)
    - Ad Orientem; Sussex, England (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - X346 A213, 1960-1967; nos. 33-80, 27 catalogs
    - The Adelphi Book Shop LTD.; Victoria, B.C., Canada (Box 3, Folder 21-26)
  - X346 A2135, 1977-1986; unnumbered, 6 catalogs
    - Richard H. Adelson; North Pomfret, Vermont (Box 3, Folder 27-28)
  - X346 A2145, undated; nos. 23-45, 20 catalogs
    - Arno Adler; Lübeck (Box 4, Folder 29-32)
  - X346 A215, 1943-1959; nos. 19-157, 71 catalogs
    - Arthur M. Adler; New York, N.Y. (Box 4, Folder 33-36)
    - Arthur M. Adler; New York, N.Y. (Box 5, Folder 37-41)
  - X346 A24 I, undated, 1888-1973; unnumbered, 21 catalogs.+7 price lists
    - Adrien-Maisonneuve; Paris (Box 5, Folder 42-44)
    - Adrien-Maisonneuve; Paris (Box 6, Folder 45-46)
  - X346 A24 II, 1927-1965; nos. 3-58, 49 catalogs
    - Adrien-Maisonneuve; Paris (Box 6, Folder 47-52)
    - Adrien-Maisonneuve; Paris (Box 7, Folder 53-57)
  - X346 A28, 1962-1963; nos. 81-85, 4 catalogs
    - Librairie Africaine Hubaut; Bruxelles (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - X346 A29, 1952-1959; unnumbered, 20 catalogs
    - Africa Books; Basutoland, S. Africa (Box 7, Folder 59-60)
  - X346 A315, 1939-1961; nos. 9-20, 24 catalogs
    - Alabama Book Store (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Alabama Book Store (Box 8, Folder 62-63)
  - X346 A355, undated; nos. 1-125, 43 catalogs
    - The Americanist; Lansdowne, Pennyslvania (Box 8, Folder 64-67)
  - X346 A36, 1912-1971; unnumbered, 28 catalogs
    - The Aldine Book Company; Brooklyn, N. Y. (Box 9, Folder 68-72)
  - X346 A368, 1964-ca. 1977; nos. 22-74, 10 catalogs
    - The Aldredge Book Store; Dallas, Texas (Box 9, Folder 73-74)
  - X346 A42, 1871-1966; nos. start after 1949 [1-44], 67 catalogs
    - EDW. G. Allen; Covent Garden, London (Box 10, Folder 75-80)
    - EDW. G. Allen; Covent Garden, London (Box 11, Folder 81-85)
  - X346 A435, undated, 1933-1934; nos. 2-608, 20 catalogs
    - J. A. Allen Co.; London, England (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - J. A. Allen Co.; London, England (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - X346 A435 I, undated; nos. 1-16, 16 catalogs
    - J. A. Allen Co.; London, England (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - X346 A435 II, undated; nos. 1-11, 12 catalogs
    - J. A. Allen Co.; London, England (Box 12, Folder 89-90)
  - X346 A425 III, undated; no. 1, 1 catalog
    - J. A. Allen Co.; London, England (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - X346 A425 IV, undated, 1932-1935; unnumbered, 6 catalogs
    - J. A. Allen Co.; London, England (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - X346 A428, 1918-1987; nos. 1-276, 188 catalogs
    - William H. Allen; Philadelphia (Box 12, Folder 93-94)
    - William H. Allen; Philadelphia (Box 13, Folder 95-100)
    - William H. Allen; Philadelphia (Box 14, Folder 101-106)
    - William H. Allen; Philadelphia (Box 15, Folder 107-111)
    - William H. Allen; Philadelphia (Box 16, Folder 112-116)
  - X346 A467, 1824; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - J. Altheer; Hollande (Box 16, Folder 117)
  - X346 A477, undated, 1957-1963, undated; nos. 6-115, 104 catalogs
    - Amelang; Frankfurt Am Main (Box 17, Folder 118-123)
    - Amelang; Frankfurt Am Main (Box 18, Folder 124-129)
    - Amelang; Frankfurt Am Main (Box 19, Folder 130-133)
  - X346 A483 I, 1934-1943; unnumbered, 80 catalogs
    - The American Autograph Shop; Ridley Park, Pennsylvannia (Box 19, Folder 134-135)
    - The American Autograph Shop; Ridley Park, Pennsylvannia (Box 20, Folder 136-141)
    - The American Autograph Shop; Ridley Park, Pennsylvannia (Box 21, Folder 142-146)
  - X346 A483 II, 1929; vol. 5:1, 1 catalog
    - The American Autograph Shop; Ridley Park, Pennsylvannia (Box 21, Folder 147)
  - X346 A483 III, 1935-1937; unnumbered, 4 catalogs
    - The American Autograph Shop; Ridley Park, Pennsylvannia (Box 21, Folder 148)
  - X346 A489, 1952-1962; nos. 11-175, 9 catalogs
    - American Scholar; New York, N.Y. (Box 22, Folder 149)
  - X346 A495, 1938; no. 1, 1 catalog
    - Americana Canadiana; Montreal, Can. (Box 22, Folder 150)
  - X346 A51, 1902-undated; nos. 7-85, 27 catalogs
    - Americus Book Co.; Americus, GA. (Box 22, Folder 151-157)
  - X346 A53 I, 1949-1953, undated; nos. 8-27, 12 catalogs
    - Bernard Amtmann; Ottawa, Canada (Box 22, Folder 158)
  - X346 A53 III, 1954-1969; nos. 18-258, 161 catalogs
    - Bernard Amtmann; Ottawa, Canada (Box 23, Folder 159-163)
    - Bernard Amtmann; Ottawa, Canada (Box 24, Folder 164-170)
    - Bernard Amtmann; Ottawa, Canada (Box 25, Folder 171-176)
    - Bernard Amtmann; Ottawa, Canada (Box 26, Folder 177-182)
    - Bernard Amtmann; Ottawa, Canada (Box 27, Folder 183-184)
  - X346 A53 IV, 1964; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Bernard Amtmann; Ottawa, Canada (Box 27, Folder 185)
  - X346 A56, undated; no. 46, 1 catalog
    - Antiquariat K. André; Prag (Box 27, Folder 186)
  - X346 A572, 1845; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - William Andrews; Bristol (Box 27, Folder 187)
  - X346 A59, 1963-1969; unnumbered, 6 catalogs
    - Angus Robertson LTD; Sydney, Australia (Box 27, Folder 188-189)
  - X346 A62, 1915-undated; nos. 8-65, 46 catalogs
    Scope and Contents
    Location varies. Name variant: E. Woodland; West Kirby, England
    - Antiquarian Book Co.; Birmingham, England (Box 27, Folder 190)
    - Antiquarian Book Co.; Birmingham, England (Box 28, Folder 191-193)
  - X346 A62 II, undated; unnumbered, 16 catalogs
    - Antiquarian Book Co.; Birmingham, England (Box 28, Folder 194)
  - X346 A620, 1905-1908; nos. 11-52, 23 catalogs
    - The Antiquarian Book Co. London, England (Box 28, Folder 195-196)
  - X346 A627, 1963-1964; nos. 2-6, 5 catalogs
    - Ernst Apfel; N. Y., N. Y. (Box 28, Folder 197)
  - X346 A632, undated, 1929; nos. 9-11, 3 catalogs
    - Antiquariat; Weimar (Box 28, Folder 198)
  - X346 A635, undated; nos. 3-9, 4 catalogs
    - Paul P. Appel; Mamaroneck, N. Y. (Box 28, Folder 199)
  - X346 A640, undated; nos. 11-41, 30 catalogs
    - Appelfeld Gallery; New York, N.Y. (Box 29, Folder 200-203)
  - X346 A649, 1858; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - D. Appleton Co.; New York, N.Y. (Box 29, Folder 204)
  - X346 A66, undated; nos. 22-82, 41 catalogs
    - Librairie d'Argences; Paris (Box 29, Folder 205-206)
    - Librairie d'Argences; Paris (Box 30, Folder 207-211)
    - Librairie d'Argences; Paris (Box 31, Folder 212)
    - Librairie d'Argences; Paris (Box 31, Folder 213)
  - X346 A665, 1817; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - John and Arthur Arch; London (Box 31, Folder 214)
  - X346 A69, undated; nos. 6-738, 525 catalogs
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 31, Folder 215-217)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 32, Folder 218-223)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 33, Folder 224-230)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 34, Folder 231-237)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 35, Folder 238-242)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 36, Folder 243-248)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 37, Folder 249-254)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 38, Folder 255-261)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 39, Folder 262-267)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 40, Folder 268-273)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 41, Folder 274-278)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 42, Folder 279-284)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 43, Folder 285-290)
    - Argosy Book Stores, Inc.; New York City (Box 44, Folder 291-295)
  - X346 A692, 1968-undated; unnumbered, 22 catalogs
    - Argus Antiquarian Booksellers; BAARN, The Netherlands (Box 45, Folder 296-298)
  - X346 A693, undated; nos. 1-33, 29 catalogs
    - Argus Book Shop; New York, N. Y. (Box 45, Folder 299-300)
    - Argus Book Shop; New York, N. Y. (Box 46, Folder 301)
  - X346 A771, undated; nos. 1-53, 18 catalogs
    - Ars Libri, Ltd; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 46, Folder 302-307)
  - X346 A781, [1931]-undated; nos. 18-71, 47 catalogs
    - L'Art Ancien S.A.; Zurich (Box 47, Folder 308-313)
    - L'Art Ancien S.A.; Zurich (Box 48, Folder 314-316)
  - X346 A781 II, 1932-1935, undated; nos. 1-195, 38 catalogs
    - L'Art Ancien S.A.; Zurich (Box 48, Folder 317-319)
    - L'Art Ancien S.A.; Zurich (Box 49, Folder 320-322)
  - X346 A781 III, 1921-1925, undated; nos. 4-24, 5 catalogs
    - L'Art Ancien S.A.; Lugano, Switzerland (Box 49, Folder 323)
  - X346 A791, undated; nos. 1-71, 39 catalogs
    - Alta California Bookstore; Berkeley, California (Box 49, Folder 324-325)
    - Alta California Bookstore; Berkeley, California (Box 50, Folder 326-328)
  - X346 A816, 1849-1873; unnumbered, 23 catalogs
    - A. Asher Co.; Berlin (Box 50, Folder 329-330)
    - A. Asher Co.; Berlin (Box 51, Folder 331-333)
  - X346 A816 I, 1947-1977, undated; nos. 1-23, 16 catalogs
    - A. Asher Co.; Berlin (Box 51, Folder 334-335)
    - A. Asher Co.; Berlin (Box 52, Folder 336-337)
  - X346 A84, undated; nos.1-19, 11 catalogs
    - The Asphodel Book Shop; Cleveland, Ohio (Box 52, Folder 338-339)
  - X346 A843, undated; nos. 46-74, 14 catalogs
    - J. G. Aspin Bookseller; Cheshire, England (Box 52, Folder 340-341)
    - J. G. Aspin Bookseller; Cheshire, England (Box 53, Folder 342)
  - X346 A87, 1912-1933; nos. 1-96, 96 catalogs
    - Reginald Atkinson; London (Box 53, Folder 343-347)
    - Reginald Atkinson; London (Box 54, Folder 348-353)
    - Reginald Atkinson; London (Box 55, Folder 354-356)
  - X346 A882, undated; nos. 1-36, 21 catalogs
    - Atlas Book Shop; New York City (Box 55, Folder 357-358)
  - X346 A89, undated; nos. 7-114, 27 catalogs
    - Austin Book Shop; Kew Gardens, N.Y. (Box 55, Folder 359)
    - Austin Book Shop; Kew Gardens, N.Y. (Box 56, Folder 360-361)
  - X346 A935, 1887-ca. 1900; unnumbered, 3 catalogs
    - The Autotype Company; London (Box 56, Folder 362-363)
  - X346 A96, 1938-1948; unnumbered, 54 catalogs
    - Avon Books, Inc; Palisade, N.J. (Box 56, Folder 364-365)
    - Avon Books, Inc; Palisade, N.J. (Box 57, Folder 366-368)
  - X346 Ab34, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - J. Abel; Northampton (Box 57, Folder 369)
  - X346 Am 162, 1956-1976; nos. 3-34, 23 catalogs
    - Samuel Ambaras Inc.; New York, New York (Box 57, Folder 370-372)
    - Samuel Ambaras Inc.; New York, New York (Box 58, Folder 373-375)
  - X346 An875, undated; nos. 1-12, 14 catalogs
    - Antiquarian Booksellers Association; New York, N.Y. (Box 58, Folder 376-378)
    - Antiquarian Booksellers Association; New York, N.Y. (Box 59, Folder 379)
  - X346 An876, 1968, undated; nos. 1-133, 2 catalogs
    - Antiquarian Booksellers; Amsterdam, Netherlands (Box 59, Folder 380)
  - X346 An877, 1966-1976, undated; nos. 1-70, 5 catalogs + 2 supplements
    - Antiquarian Booksellers Center; New York, N. Y. (Box 59, Folder 381)
- B
  - X346 B1395, undated; nos. 1-21, 19 catalogs
    - E. Baer; London, England (Box 59, Folder 382-383)
  - X346 B14 I, 1864-undated; nos. 1-794, 286 catalogs
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 59, Folder 384-385)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 60, Folder 386-391)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 61, Folder 392-397)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 62, Folder 398-403)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 63, Folder 404-408)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 64, Folder 409-414)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 65, Folder 415-420)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 66, Folder 421-425)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 67, Folder 426-430)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 68, Folder 431-434)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 69, Folder 435-439)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 70, Folder 440-444)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 71, Folder 445-449)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 72, Folder 450-455)
  - X346 B14 II, 1899-1922; nos. 1-15, 51 catalogs
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 73, Folder 456-462)
    - Joseph Baer Co.; Frankfurt (Box 74, Folder 463-465)
  - X346 B15, 1888-1935; nos. 4-147, 50 catalogs
    - Bailey Brothers; London, England (Box 74, Folder 466)
    - Bailey Brothers; London, England (Box 75, Folder 467-470)
  - X346 B151, 1950; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Bailey Brothers Swinfen LTD.; London (Box 76, Folder 471)
  - X346 B157, 1842; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - H. Bailliere; London (Box 76, Folder 472)
  - X346 B1695, 1962-1967; nos. 3-11, 8 catalogs
    - C. G. Baker Fine Books; Bath, England (Box 76, Folder 473)
  - X346 B17, 1920-undated; nos. 1-70, 56 catalogs
    - G. A. Baker Co.; New York City (Box 76, Folder 474-476)
    - G. A. Baker Co.; New York City (Box 77, Folder 477-480)
    - G. A. Baker Co.; New York City (Box 78, Folder 481)
  - X346 B17 II, undated; nos. 69-97, 28 catalogs
    - Baker Brooks, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 78, Folder 482-484)
  - X346 B172, undated; nos. 259-302, 17 catalogs
    - Edward Baker; Birmingham, England (Box 78, Folder 485-486)
    - Edward Baker; Birmingham, England (Box 79, Folder 487)
  - X346 B174, undated, 1852-1937; unnumbered, nos. 17-779, 222 catalogs
    - Thomas Baker; London, England (Box 79, Folder 488-491)
    - Thomas Baker; London, England (Box 80, Folder 492-496)
    - Thomas Baker; London, England (Box 81, Folder 497-501)
    - Thomas Baker; London, England (Box 82, Folder 502-506)
    - Thomas Baker; London, England (Box 83, Folder 507-510)
    - Thomas Baker; London, England (Box 84, Folder 511-513)
  - X346 B178 I, nos. 205-681, 273 catalogs
    - Baker's Bookshop; Birmingham, England (Box 84, Folder 514-515)
    - Baker's Bookshop; Birmingham, England (Box 85, Folder 516-521)
    - Baker's Bookshop; Birmingham, England (Box 86, Folder 522-527)
    - Baker's Bookshop; Birmingham, England (Box 87, Folder 528-532)
    - Baker's Bookshop; Birmingham, England (Box 88, Folder 533-536)
    - Baker's Bookshop; Birmingham, England (Box 89, Folder 537-540)
    - Baker's Bookshop; Birmingham, England (Box 90, Folder 541-545)
  - X346 B178 IV, 1930; no. 200, 1 catalog
    - Greville Worthington; Worchester (Box 91, Folder 547)
  - X346 B1892, 1973-1981; nos. 5-79, 27 catalogs
    - R J Balding (Books) LTD; Edinburgh, Scotland (Box 91, Folder 548-551)
  - X346 B1895, 1823-1848; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Robert Baldock; London (Box 92, Folder 552)
  - X346 B19, 1924-1939; nos. 250-395B, 91 catalogs
    - J. Baldwin; Essex (Box 92, Folder 553-556)
  - X346 B193, 1951-1967; nos. 6-39, 21 catalogs
    - Baldwins' Book Barn; West Chester, Pennsylvania (Box 93, Folder 561-562)
  - X346 B219, 1935-1947; nos. 6-37, 25 catalogs
    - Bamberger Wahrmann; Jerusalem (Box 94, Folder 563-566)
  - X346 B22, 1845-1871; nos. 1-3, 2 catalogs
    - Bangs, Merwin Co.; New York (Box 95, Folder 567-568)
  - X346 B2235, 1962-1965, undated; nos. 1-10, 5 catalogs
    - Banquette Book Shop; New Orleans, Louisiana (Box 95, Folder 569)
  - X346 B225, undated, 1939-1941; nos. 18-60, 43 catalogs
    - R. E. Banta; Crawfordsville, IND. (Box 95, Folder 570-572)
    - R. E. Banta; Crawfordsville, IND. (Box 96, Folder 573-574)
  - X346 B23, 1932-1959; nos. 2-40, 39 catalogs
    - Julian Barbazan; Madrid (Box 96, Folder 575-577)
    - Julian Barbazan; Madrid (Box 97, Folder 578-580)
  - X346 B233, 1952-1954; nos. 1-8, 6 catalogs
    - Piero Barbèra; Roma (Box 97, Folder 581)
  - X346 B2355, 1786; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Barde, Manget Comp. (Box 98, Folder 582)
  - X346 B25, undated; nos. 12-182, 162 catalogs
    - P. M. Barnard, M.A.; Tunbridge Wells, England (Box 98, Folder 583-586)
    - P. M. Barnard, M.A.; Tunbridge Wells, England (Box 99, Folder 587-591)
    - P. M. Barnard, M.A.; Tunbridge Wells, England (Box 100, Folder 592-596)
    - P. M. Barnard, M.A.; Tunbridge Wells, England (Box 101, Folder 597-601)
  - X346 B258, 1934-1970, undated; nos. 201-602, 234 catalogs
    - Barnes Noble, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 102, Folder 602-606)
    - Barnes Noble, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 103, Folder 607-610)
    - Barnes Noble, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 104, Folder 611-615)
    - Barnes Noble, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 105, Folder 616-620)
    - Barnes Noble, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 106, Folder 621-624)
    - Barnes Noble, Inc.; New York, N. Y. (Box 107, Folder 625-629)
  - X346 B267, 1949-ca. 1971; unnumbered, 32 catalogs
    - J. N. Bartfield; New York, N. Y. (Box 108, Folder 630-633)
    - J. N. Bartfield; New York, N. Y. (Box 109, Folder 634-636)
  - X346 B276, undated; nos. 18-31, 11 catalogs + 2 map supplements
    - Peter Barrie; Sutton Coldfield, England (Box 109, Folder 637)
  - X346 B277, 1813; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - C. J. Barrington; London (Box 109, Folder 638)
  - X346 B28, 1904-1930; nos. 15-89, 42 catalogs
    - N. J. Bartlett Co.; Boston, Mass. (Box 110, Folder 639-641)
  - X346 B282, 1840, undated; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Bartlett Welford; New York (Box 110, Folder 642)
  - X346 B312, 1974[?]-1986[?]; nos. 6-58, 21 catalogs
    - Robert F. Batchelder; Ambler, Penna. (Box 110, Folder 643)
    - Robert F. Batchelder; Ambler, Penna. (Box 111, Folder 644-645)
  - X346 B313, undated; nos. 1-31, 32 catalogs
    - George Bates; Sussex (Box 111, Folder 646-647)
    - George Bates; Sussex (Box 112, Folder 648-649)
  - X346 B317, 1903-1919; nos. 1-40, 1 catalog
    - Joan Bta. Battle; Barcelona (Box 113, Folder 650)
  - X346 B322, undated, 1948-1954; nos. 8-23, 8 catalogs
    - B. T. Batsford, LTD.; London (Box 114, Folder 651)
  - X346 B322 I, 1936-1961; nos. 101-121, 19 catalogs
    - B. T. Batsford, LTD.; London (Box 114, Folder 652-654)
    - B. T. Batsford, LTD.; London (Box 115, Folder 655)
  - X346 B322 II, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - B. T. Batsford, LTD.; London (Box 115, Folder 656)
  - X346 B323, 1965-1978; nos. 1-20, 13 catalogs
    - David Battan; Fresno, California (Box 115, Folder 657)
  - X346 B342, 1816-1829; unnumbered, 6 catalogs
    - W. Baynes; London (Box 115, Folder 658)
    - W. Baynes; London (Box 116, Folder 659)
  - X346 B3495, undated; nos. 1-6, 6 catalogs
    - Maurice Bazy; Paris (Box 116, Folder 660)
  - X346 B3535, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - D. M. Beach; Salisbury (Box 116, Folder 661)
  - X346 B38, 1947-ca. 1962; nos. 2-31, 29 catalogs
    - The Beauchamp Bookshop LTD.; London, England (Box 116, Folder 662-663)
  - X346 B386, 1832; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - De Feu M. Le Marquis De Beauvoir; Paris (Box 116, Folder 664)
  - X346 B3915, undated-1986; nos. 1-41, 35 catalogs
    - Beeleigh Abbey; Maldon, Essex (Box 117, Folder 665-668)
    - Beeleigh Abbey; Maldon, Essex (Box 118, Folder 669)
  - X346 B392, 1791-1801; unnumbered, 4 catalogs
    - Isaac Beers; New Haven (Box 118, Folder 670-671)
  - X346 B397, 1948-1957; nos. 55-106, 67 catalogs
    - J. L. Beijers; Utrecht (Box 118, Folder 672-673)
    - J. L. Beijers; Utrecht (Box 119, Folder 674-677)
    - J. L. Beijers; Utrecht (Box 120, Folder 678-679)
  - X346 B399 I, 1889-1932; nos. 145-380, 23 catalogs
    - Théophile Belin; Paris (Box 120, Folder 680-684)
    - Théophile Belin; Paris (Box 121, Folder 685)
  - X346 B399 II, 1897-1902; unnumbered, 4 catalogs
    - Théophile Belin; Paris (Box 121, Folder 686-688)
  - X346 B346, 1818; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - John Bell; Newcastle (Box 121, Folder 689)
  - X346 B417, 1926-undated; nos. 1-36, 27 catalogs
    - H. W. Belmore; Rome (Box 122, Folder 690-691)
  - X346 B4383, 1840; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - T. Bennett; London (Box 122, Folder 692)
  - X346 B451, 1935-1979, undated; nos. 10-76, 44 catalogs
    - Pierre Berès; Paris (Box 122, Folder 693-694)
    - Pierre Berès; Paris (Box 123, Folder 695-698)
    - Pierre Berès; Paris (Box 124, Folder 699-702)
    - Pierre Berès; Paris (Box 125, Folder 703-704)
  - X346 B451 II, 1958-1967; nos. 8-110, 49 catalogs
    - Pierre Berès; Paris (Box 125, Folder 705)
  - X346 B4537, 1951-1969; nos. 26-45, 16 catalogs
    - Isaiah Berger; Brooklyn, N.Y. (Box 126, Folder 706)
  - X346 B4554, 1956-undated; nos. 9-251, 63 catalogs
    - Messrs. Berkelouw; Sydney, Australia (Box 126, Folder 707-710)
    - Messrs. Berkelouw; Sydney, Australia (Box 127, Folder 711-712)
  - X346 B4565, 1965-1968; unnumbered, 7 catalogs
    - Bernard Frèrejean (Box 127, Folder 713)
  - X346 B457, 1945-1986; nos. 2-251, 194 catalogs
    - F. A. Bernett; New York, N.Y. (Box 127, Folder 714-715)
    - F. A. Bernett; New York, N.Y. (Box 128, Folder 716-721)
    - F. A. Bernett; New York, N.Y. (Box 129, Folder 722-726)
    - F. A. Bernett; New York, N.Y. (Box 130, Folder 727-729)
  - X346 B4598, 1958-1961; nos. 17-35, 18 catalogs
    - Donald A. Berry; London (Box 130, Folder 730-731)
  - X346 B4598 I, 1956-1969; nos. 1-32, 25 catalogs
    - Donald A. Berry; London (Box 131, Folder 732-734)
  - X346 B4599, 1953-1962; nos. 1-63, 13 catalogs
    - Georges Berthier; Arcachon (Box 131, Folder 735)
  - X346 B46, 1888-1913; nos. 3-75, 24 catalogs
    - Richard Bertling; Dresden (Box 131, Folder 736)
    - Richard Bertling; Dresden (Box 132, Folder 737-739)
  - X346 B464, 1908-1936; nos. 7-96, 54 catalogs
    - Albert Besombes; Paris (Box 132, Folder 740-742)
    - Albert Besombes; Paris (Box 133, Folder 743-747)
  - X346 B468, 1956-1957; nos. 28-30, 3 catalogs
    - Biblion, Inc; Forest Hills, N. Y. (Box 133, Folder 748)
  - X346 B4717, 1936-undated; nos. 1-251, 108 catalogs
    - Biblio Tannen; New York, N. Y. (Box 133, Folder 749-750)
    - Biblio Tannen; New York, N. Y. (Box 134, Folder 751-756)
    - Biblio Tannen; New York, N. Y. (Box 135, Folder 757-759)
  - X346 B473, 1952-1962; nos. 8-18, 9 catalogs
    - Tamara Bieber; Quaker Hill, Connecticut (Box 135, Folder 760)
  - X346 B486, 1837; no. 6, 1 catalog
    - Bignon; Paris (Box 135, Folder 761)
  - X346 B538, undated; nos. 6-44, 40 catalogs
    - Birrell Garnett LTD.; London (Box 135, Folder 762-763)
    - Birrell Garnett LTD.; London (Box 136, Folder 764-766)
  - X346 B558, 1906-1985; nos. 50-519, 124 catalogs
    - Björck Börjesson; Stockholm (Box 136, Folder 767-769)
    - Björck Börjesson; Stockholm (Box 137, Folder 770-774)
    - Björck Börjesson; Stockholm (Box 138, Folder 775-779)
    - Björck Börjesson; Stockholm (Box 139, Folder 780-785)
    - Björck Börjesson; Stockholm (Box 140, Folder 786-791)
    - Björck Börjesson; Stockholm (Box 141, Folder 792-794)
  - X346 B5582, 1817-1819; unnumbered, 3 catalogs
    - Adam Black; Edinburgh (Box 141, Folder 795)
  - X346 B56 I, 1895-1980; nos. 46-1144, 939 catalogs
    - B. H. Blackwell; Oxford (Box 142, Folder 796-800)
    - B. H. Blackwell; Oxford (Box 143, Folder 801-805)
    - B. H. Blackwell; Oxford (Box 144, Folder 806-811)
    - B. H. Blackwell; Oxford (Box 145, Folder 812-816)
    - B. H. Blackwell; Oxford (Box 146, Folder 817-821)